Md. Golam Mostafa

Full Stack Software Engineer (.Net Developer).





+ 8801886621899

gmostafa358@gmail.com

17, Dogair, Demra Dhaka1261.

CAREER SUMMARY

I am Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP), Experienced in financial solutions with .NET & Other Cutting-Edge Technology. 8.3+ years of professional experience in developing ERP like Human Resource, Payroll, Inventory, Accounting, CRM, Provident Fund for Garments/Textiles/Spinning /Manufacturing Industries, Corporate & MNC.

PROFESSIONAL EXPEIENCE (8-year 3 months(s))

Senior Software Engineer- July 2022 to Present

Hydrus Digital BD (Pvt) Ltd. / Dhaka

Responsibilities:

- Lead Team, Supervise the subordinate's activities
- Requirement's collection & analysis
- System& Database Design
- Design and develop APIs
- Review and debug code, perform validation and verification testing
- Identify and suggest various opportunities to improve efficiency and functionality. Collaborate with internal teams and clients to fix and improve products.

Software Engineer- March, 2022 - July, 2022

ESOL BD Ltd

Dhanmondi/ Dhaka

Responsibilities:

- Collaborate with product managers to translate end-user requirements into technical specifications
- Participate in software presentation & Training

Programmer - May 2018 to Jun, 2022

KKDestiny . / Jessore

Responsibilities:

- Design overall architecture of the web application
- Requirement's collection & analysis
- System & Database Design
- Write clean, functional code on the front- and back-end

Jr. Programmer- Aug 2015 to April, 2018

General Automation Ltd. / Dhaka

Responsibilities:

- Assisting the development manager with all aspects of software design and Coding, Test and fix bugs or other coding issues
- Maintain existing software programs, make approved changes

SKILLS

C#

Microservice Windows Forms Windows Service ADO.NET **ASP.NET** ASP.NET MVC ASP.NET Core

Web API **Entity Framework** LINQ

Angular, TypeScript HTML, CSS, Bootstrap jQuery, JavaScript

Crystal Report, RDLC Report, VBReport8, GrapeCity

SQL Server, MySQL, **PostgreSQL** TFS, GIT

Accounting Finance **Human Resource** Management

Credit Collection Officer - Oct 2013 to April, 2014 City bank Ltd. / Dhaka

• Follow-up customer, Inquire customer information, Credit Risk Analysis, Credit recovery.

REMARKABLE PROJECTS

Patients Management System:

It refers to several efficient automated systems that track patient information, diagnoses, prescriptions, interactions and encounters. Technologies: Asp.net core Api, Angular

Lease Finance:

DOMAIN

KNOWLEDGE

ERP

Health Care

Human Resource

Payroll

Inventory

Accounting Lease Finance

Highway Toll

Management Systems

CRM
Provident Fund

GitHub Link

Lease financial Solution for Japanese Client.

Technologies: C#, Windows Form, Spiral Api, VBReport8 Report

Highway Toll Management Systems:

The project is maintenance of the toll collection systems at the core of expressways extend throughout Japan as major arteries, this expressway network.

Technologies: MVC4, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL Server, VBReport8 Report

Citizen Registration in Japan:

Features: Citizen Registration and update Information. Technologies: C#, Design and develop APIs, MS SQL 2016

Invoice Generation for Highway Toll:

Features: Data import and Invoice Generation.

Technologies: C#, VBReport8 Report

GAL ERP:

Features: Personnel Management, Training, Performance Appraisal, Attendance, Leave, Payroll, Provident Fund, Loan Management, Marketing, Sales, Purchase, Inventory, Billing, Accounts, Documents Management

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET MVC, jQuery, SQL Server, Crystal Report

Attendance, Leave and Payroll Software:

Features: Attendance, Leave and Payroll

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Web, SQL Server, Crystal Report

Access Control Management:

Features: Register & Mapping user to Biometric Device, User Access Control, Integration of Attendance Data with SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL

Technologies: C#, Windows Form, Windows Service, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL, MySQL

Inventory System:

Features: Inventory, Purchase

Technologies: MVC4, Crystal reports, MS SQL 2012, VS 2012

School Management System:

Features: Student& Teacher Info, Admission, Academic, Exam &

Management, Payment, Attendance, HR

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Web Form, jQuery, SQL Server, RDLC Report

EDUCATION

2016- Post Graduate Diploma in ICT

Bangladesh Computer Council

2015-Diploma in Enterprise System Analysis and Design (C#)

IDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Project, Round-22

2011-BBA

National University, SAFS Business Institute.

2007- H.S.C

Business Studies, Dhaka Board

2005-SSC

Business Studies, Dhaka Board

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS:

2015- Web Development in Php

BASIS Institute of Technology & Management (BITM)

2014- Soft Core-Training

City Bank Ltd

2009- Natural English

Saifurs

Transcript Link

CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Certified

Solutions Developer

(MCSD). Year-2015

Microsoft Certified

Solutions Associate

(MCSA)

Year - 2016

OTHERS SKILL

- Experience on standalone project development, complicated database design and development, writing complex store procedures, triggers, views with SQL Server.
- Experience in Developing ERP.
- Good analytical & problem-solving skills.
- Supplied superior customer service & training.

PERSONAL INFO

DOB

Marital Status Home District - March 15, 1990

- Married

- Dhaka

REFERENCE

Muhammad Atiqur Rahman

Senior Programmer

KK Destiny

Sheikh Hasina Software Technology

Park (3th floor), Jessore.

Mobile: 01717834129

Email: atiqur.rahman@kkdestiny.com

MD. Nazrul Islam

Senior Software Engineer

Subra Systems Ltd

93/4A, Zigatola, Dhaka-1209

Mobile: 01914945615 Email: nijewel@live.com

MD. GOLAM MOSTAFA